{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Security Camera Installation \u0026 Repair Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40409/":{"taskOID":40409,"originalTaskOID":40409,"setID":702,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4461,"questionDisplayText":"Need for Camera","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you want a video security system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4949,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Protection from property loss","answerDisplayText":"Protection from property loss","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4948,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Protect occupants","answerDisplayText":"Protect occupants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3907,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Monitor children","answerDisplayText":"Monitor children","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3908,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Monitor household help","answerDisplayText":"Monitor household help","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4462,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Cameras Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many cameras do you think you'll need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":398,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":541,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-10","answerDisplayText":"6-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4463,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Video Surveillance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of video surveillance do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5068,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Recorded","answerDisplayText":"Recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4294,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Not recorded","answerDisplayText":"Not recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2304,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exposed cameras","answerDisplayText":"Exposed cameras","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hidden cameras","answerDisplayText":"Hidden cameras","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":891,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Audio/video cameras","answerDisplayText":"Audio/video cameras","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4461,"questionDisplayText":"Need for Camera","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you want a video security system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4949,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Protection from property loss","answerDisplayText":"Protection from property loss","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4948,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Protect occupants","answerDisplayText":"Protect occupants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3907,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Monitor children","answerDisplayText":"Monitor children","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3908,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Monitor household help","answerDisplayText":"Monitor household help","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4949,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Protection from property loss","answerDisplayText":"Protection from property loss","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4948,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Protect occupants","answerDisplayText":"Protect occupants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3907,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Monitor children","answerDisplayText":"Monitor children","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3908,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Monitor household help","answerDisplayText":"Monitor household help","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4462,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Cameras Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many cameras do you think you'll need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":398,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":541,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-10","answerDisplayText":"6-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":398,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":541,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-10","answerDisplayText":"6-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4463,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Video Surveillance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of video surveillance do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5068,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Recorded","answerDisplayText":"Recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4294,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Not recorded","answerDisplayText":"Not recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2304,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exposed cameras","answerDisplayText":"Exposed cameras","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hidden cameras","answerDisplayText":"Hidden cameras","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":891,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Audio/video cameras","answerDisplayText":"Audio/video cameras","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5068,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Recorded","answerDisplayText":"Recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4294,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Not recorded","answerDisplayText":"Not recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2304,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exposed cameras","answerDisplayText":"Exposed cameras","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hidden cameras","answerDisplayText":"Hidden cameras","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":891,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Audio/video cameras","answerDisplayText":"Audio/video cameras","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40409/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40409,"taskName":"Surveillance Cameras - Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install, Service, or Repair Surveillance Cameras","xmTaskDescriptor":"Security Camera Installation \u0026 Repair Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":310,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Security burglar protection sercuirty secure","textMessagingName":"Surveil Camera","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically used to monitor entrances, perimeters, the ill \u0026 small children. Cameras are mounted \u0026 connected to monitors \u0026/or taping equipment.","rolloverShortDesc":"Used for remote monitoring of people \u0026 possessions.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install, Service, or Repair Surveillance Cameras.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e Surveillance Cameras Install | Video Camera Repair Service \u003cin_city\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":67,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Surveillance Camera Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Surveillance Cameras - Install or Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Surveillance Camera Project","urlName":"Surveillance-Cameras-Install-or-Repair","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Security Camera Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Repair Surveillance Cameras","searchKeywords":"Security,burglar,protection,sercuirty,secure,safe,protect,systems,alarms,Cameras,system,Surveillance","emcCategoryOid":-12043,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":702,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}